

MUHARDIANSYAH

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

CONTACT

+62 822-8423-1585

muhardiansyah97@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/muhardiansyah15

(©) @muhardiansyah15

Kota Batam, Kepulauan Riau, Indonesia 29444

https://muhardiansyah.netlify.app

SKILLS

- Expert in **Odoo** ERP software and architecture
- Proficient in Python, PostgreSQL, and MySQL
- Experienced in PHP, HTML, and CSS for web development
- Familiar with version control tools GIT, Github, Gitlab, and SVN
- Knowledgeable in **Ubuntu** operating system for server administration
- Skilled in R programming for data analysis and statistics

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Mathematics

Universitas Andalas, Padang

2015-2019

English

GPA 3.17 out of 4.00

LANGUAGES

ABOUT ME

With over 3 years of experience as a software engineer at a software house company, I have developed expertise in ERP software. My focus has been on backend development, and I have developed proficiency in Accounting, MRP, Inventory Management, Sales, and Customer Relationship Management (CRM) functionalities within ERP systems. Additionally, I possess strong programming skills in Python, PostgreSQL, and MySQL, and I am well-versed in web development technologies such as PHP, HTML, and CSS.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Odoo Developer

PT BION DIGITAL INDONESIA, JAKARTA

May 2023 - present

- Design, develop, and testing Odoo Modules
- Perform testing of new functions or modifications
- · Perform system integration testing and unit testing.
- · Perform data migration.
- Perform configuration, installation, and maintenance of server and multi database Odoo environment
- · Complete and clear documentation of every tasks.
- Perform L1, L3 and L2 Support
- Provide best possible solutions for client needs.
- · Perform ad-hoc duties

Software Engineer

PT TIGERNIX SOLUTIONS INDONESIA, BATAM

March 2021 - May 2023

- Have good knowledge of Odoo's framework and its functionalities, ORM systems, PostgreSQL, and Python programming language.
- Skilled in customizing existing modules, and developing custom solutions.
- Proficient in using SVN for version control and collaboration.
- Knowledgeable in using the Ubuntu operating system.
- Experienced in project management and addressing customer issues.
- Skilled in diagnosing and resolving software bugs in ERP systems.
- Extensive experienced in working with remote server clients.
- Experienced in deploying and configuring applications on remote servers, as well as managing backups.

Software Engineer

PT INTEK KARYA, BATAM

August 2019 - February 2021

- Have good knowledge of Odoo's framework and its functionalities, ORM systems, PostgreSQL, and Python programming language.
- Skilled in customizing existing modules, and developing custom solutions.
- Proficient in using SVN for version control and collaboration.
- Knowledgeable in using the Ubuntu operating system.
- Experienced in project management and addressing customer issues.
- Skilled in diagnosing and resolving software bugs in ERP systems.
- Extensive experienced in working with remote server clients.
- Experienced in deploying and configuring applications on remote servers, as well as managing backups.